Dad, your breakfast is really the best.
果然爸爸做的早餐最好吃了
I really admire you.
佩服得五體投地啊
-But you can't eat my breakfast forever. -Why?
-但妳不能一直吃我做的早餐啊 -為什麼？
You have to be the one making breakfast when you get married.
妳結婚之後 就輪到妳做早餐給別人吃了
That's still a long way off.
這事還早呢
I saved this omelet for last.
我特地留到最後才吃的玉子燒
Mai Hanasaki.
花咲舞
What is it? You sound serious.
怎麼了？幹嘛這麼嚴肅？
I was thinking about many things, but I really think Mr. Matsuki
我考慮了很多 我認為妳要找對象的話
is the best for you.
松木是最適合妳的
A man like him is hard to find.
像他這樣的男人不多了
And I also found out that he likes fishing.
而且，我還發現他也喜歡釣魚
He has the same hobby as me.
跟我的愛好一樣呢
Your hobby has nothing to do with this.
跟你的愛好有什麼關係？
Yes, it does. Marriage will fail if families can't get along.
當然有關係，無法和家人愉快相處 有可能導致婚姻失敗
It's no use for you to get fired up over this.
你那麼興致勃勃也是沒用的
Nothing will start unless the couple themselves want to pursue it.
當事人雙方都必須感興趣 才有開始的可能
Oh, no. I'm late.
糟糕，我要遲到了
Don't worry. I'll do it.
行了，放著吧
I'm off.
那我走了
-Take care. -Okay.
-路上小心 -好
I forgot to eat that omelet I saved for last.
玉子燒，我留到最後才吃的
I should have eaten it.
應該吃了再出門的
What are you wailing about this early in the morning.
妳幹嘛一大早就哀聲嘆氣？
-What's this about the egg? -Nothing.
-雞蛋怎麼了？ -沒什麼
Bad news, guys.
大事不好了
What's wrong, Mr. Shibasaki?
怎麼了，芝崎次長？
Go to the Gotanda Branch now.
你們馬上去一趟五反田分行
Gotanda Branch?
五反田分行？
Is that the one where Mr. Matsuki is working?
就是松木先生 工作的那間五反田分行嗎？
Yes.
沒錯
Thanks to Dad, I'm super conscious now.
都怪爸爸啦，搞得我莫名在意了起來
What happened at the Gotanda Branch?
五反田分行出什麼事了？
Apparently, a customer's financial information was leaked.
有位客戶的財務資訊洩露出去了
-Really? -Yes.
-真的嗎？ -是的
Someone sent a fax to the Branch Manager.
有個人發了一張傳真給分行經理
It was a financial document managed by the branch office.
內容是該分行管理的財務資料
This is a big problem.
這可是個大問題啊
Information leaked from our bank.
我們銀行洩露了資訊呢
Information…
資訊…
Leakage…
洩露
Hey, it's leaking!
喂，漏出來了…
TOKYO DAIICHI BANK GOTANDA BRANCH
（東京第一銀行五反田分行）
I don't feel like going in.
感覺不是很想進去呢
What are you doing? Let's go.
妳在幹嘛呢？進去了
Yes.
是
Excuse me.
打擾了
I am Hanasaki, from…
我是分行稽核班的花咲…
-Mr. Matsuki? -Ms. Hanasaki.
-松木先生 -花咲小姐
You're in charge of the company from which the information leaked?
所以 被洩露資訊的公司是你負責的？
Yes.
是的
I am Takeuchi, the Branch Manager.
我是分行經理竹內
I am so sorry for this.
真的十分慚愧
We're placed in a very serious situation.
我們目前的情況真的非常棘手
I am Kadota, from the Finance Department.
我是融資課課長門田
This is the fax I received.
這就是我收到的傳真
May I see it?
請讓我看看
CLIENT'S FINANCIAL STATEMENT
（客戶財務資訊）
Sure enough it seems to be a part of our credit file.
很明顯是我們銀行信用檔案的一部分
Credit file is a document that manages all the company information, right?
信用檔案是匯總並管理 所有企業資訊的文件，對吧？
It's an important document containing all information about the company
沒錯，這是很重要的文件 包含了所有的企業資訊
such as business overview, shareholder composition,
例如企業概要、股東構成
and financial conditions.
以及財務狀況等等
Why was such an important document leaked?
那麼重要的文件怎麼會洩露了呢？
I took the credit files out yesterday
其實，我昨天想在家裡加班
because I wanted to work at home.
就把信用檔案帶出去了
What?
什麼？
Did you leave it somewhere?
你將它掉在哪裡了嗎？
No, I had the file with me in a small paper bag.
不，我將檔案放進一個紙袋裡帶走的
I didn't lose anything other than the file.
當中只有這份檔案遺失了
Then does that mean it was stolen?
所以是被偷了嗎？
What have you done?
你真是的！
I am sorry.
真的十分抱歉
What does the culprit want?
犯人的目的是什麼呢？
Actually, I just received a phone call.
其實，我剛剛接到一通電話
-Did you see the fax? -Yes.
-看過傳真了嗎？ -是的
I found this file. This belongs to your bank, right.
這份資料是我撿到的 應該是你們銀行的東西吧？
Yes. Thank you very much.
是的，十分感謝
Can I get a reward?
有酬金嗎？
What?
什麼？
Usually people get a reward for returning a lost item.
通常把失物物歸原主的話 都會有酬金的吧？
How much will you pay?
你們能給多少？
How much?
多少嗎？
It looks like an important document, so how about a million yen?
看起來是很重要的資料呢 就100萬日元吧
A million?
100萬？
I can't decide by myself.
這個我沒辦法做決定
Would it be okay if I put this up on the internet?
那我將這個放到網上去也沒關係嗎？
Oh, no…
不要
If people know that you lost this, it will damage your bank's trust.
要是被人知道你們弄丟了這種東西 銀行的聲譽應該會受損吧？
Please wait, don't do that.
等等，請別這麼做
I will call you again tomorrow.
我明天會再聯繫你們的
How terrible.
太過分了
She said she found it even though she stole it.
明明是偷的，還說是撿到的
There is no way that we can pay a million yen.
我們不可能付100萬啊
If we really pay, it will be a big minus point for the branch.
要是真的付了 分行的帳就會出現很大的虧損
Branch Manager, let's report this to the police.
竹內經理，不如我們報警吧
But…
可是…
She said she found it.
對方說是撿到的
We have no evidence that it was stolen.
我們沒有證據能證明對方是偷的
That is true, but…
話是這麼說…
Although it was indirect, she is demanding money.
雖然委婉了一些，但她的目的就是錢
I think it's better to report this to the police.
我認為還是報警比較好
-The credit file was stolen? -Yes.
-信用檔案被偷了？ -是的
What's wrong with their information management?
他們的資訊管理到底是怎麼做的？
It's unacceptable.
完全無法接受
Branch Inspection is there to solve this issue.
分行稽核班正在處理此事
-Branch Inspection? -Yes.
-分行稽核班？ -是的
We just made news with the embezzlement at Roppongi Branch.
六本木分行不久前才發生盜用事件
A scandal about a data breach is unacceptable.
這種時期絕對不能 再傳出資訊洩露這種醜聞
-Am I right? -Exactly.
-對吧？ -說得沒錯
Kodama.
兒玉
As you already know,
我想你也應該明白
make sure to settle this issue in-house.
這件事還是私下解決比較好
What do you mean by in-house?
私下解決的意思是…
In-house means in-house.
私下解決的意思就是私下解決
In-house. Yes!
私下解決，好的
I guess we have to report it.
還是報警吧
Branch Manager!
經理
Excuse me.
不好意思
-Yes? -Soma?
-喂？ -相馬
You're at the Gotanda Branch, right?
你現在在五反田分行吧？
Yes. What's up?
是的，怎麼了？
How is it? Do you think you can settle it?
如何？事情能解決嗎？
It's not that easy.
不，情況有點複雜
Listen. Don't even think about reporting it to the police.
聽好了，絕對不要報警
What?
什麼？
If you report it to the police it will become public,
報警的話，這件事就會被公開了
and people will lose their trust in Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
東京第一銀行的信用就會一落千丈
We have to avoid that.
一定要避免出現這種情況
However…
可是…
This is an order from Executive Director Shindo.
這是真藤常務的命令
Make sure to settle it in-house.
請一定要私下解決
Hey, Kodama.
喂，兒玉…
What did Mr. Kodama say?
兒玉次長說什麼了？
For the time being,
以目前的狀況來看
we have one more day because she said she will call tomorrow.
對方說明天會再聯繫 也就是說我們還有一天的時間
We can decide
我們可以等明天
whether to call the police or not after that call.
接了那通電話之後 再決定要不要報警吧
He did say something.
果然是被下了命令呢
Plus, it's not easy to steal just the credit file from the paper bag.
而且，要從紙袋裡只偷走信用檔案 可不是一件容易的事
So if we check Mr. Matsuki's activities yesterday…
我們可以查查松木先生昨天的行蹤
Then we will be able to narrow down the suspects.
那應該就能找出嫌疑人了
Please do so.
那就拜託你們這樣辦吧
Please cooperate and help them.
你來協助他們解決此事
Please go and explain this situation to Sawada Kengyou.
請向澤田建業好好解釋清楚情況
Yes.
是
Please help us.
拜託你們了
I'm working on a proposal for Sawada Kengyou's additional loan.
最近我正在準備 澤田建業追加融資的提案書
Their target loan day was on the 20th,
他們希望20號能拿到貸款
so I wanted to finish it yesterday.
所以我趕著在昨天完成
But I couldn't finish it within business hours.
但是，工作時間內實在是做不完
You took out the credit file to finish the document at home?
於是你就把信用檔案帶出去 想在家加班？
You're an amateur.
簡直是菜鳥啊
How long are you taking to finish an application that's only 20 million yen?
只不過是個兩千萬的融資申請 你要寫多久啊？
Not only that,
而且
you even broke the rules and took the credit file out of the branch.
還違反規定 把信用檔案帶到分行外面去
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Well, Managers say not to work overtime.
上頭不讓我們在銀行加班
So I'm sure hard-working employees are taking their work back home.
工作積極的職員 當然會把工作帶回家了
But that doesn't justify breaking the rules.
但這不表示可以違反規定啊
So you left the bank?
那你離開分行之後呢？
Yes. I ran into Mr. Kadota when I went out of the door.
是，從員工通道出去時 我碰到了門田課長
-Hey, Matsuki. -Yes?
-松木 -是
Great timing.
正好
I am going to dinner with Shinagawa Butsuryu. Come with me.
我現在要跟品川物流公司的人去聚餐 你也一起來吧
I thought we were turning down their loan.
我們不是決定拒絕他們的融資了嗎？
Don't worry about it. Just come with me.
不要在意這些，叫你來，你就來吧
I see. He wasn't allowed to go directly home.
所以你才無法直接回家啊？
If I knew that you had the credit file with you,
要是知道你帶著信用檔案
I wouldn't have invited you.
我就不會約你了啊
Wait a minute. You were entertained by a company
等等，你準備要拒絕他們的融資
you were about to turn down?
卻還是接受了招待嗎？
Well, yes.
那個…是的
Where did you go?
你們去了哪裡？
A Japanese restaurant named Tsujihashi in Takanawa.
高輪那裡一家叫辻橋的和食餐廳
They serve delicious crab.
他們的螃蟹很好吃哦
Did you drink?
你們喝酒了嗎？
I did.
喝了
Thank you.
謝謝
-Matsuki. -I don't…
-來，松木 -我就…
You're turning down President Kasai?
你不喝葛西社長倒的酒嗎？
-Then just a little. -Please.
-那就喝一點吧 -請
You're not a strong drinker…
你又不是很會喝
Your face turns red with just one glass of beer.
平時喝一杯啤酒臉就會通紅
How did you get home after dinner?
聚餐之後，你是怎麼回家的？
-Well… -Well?
-那個… -嗯？
We went to a bar in Gotanda after dinner.
我們聚餐後，去了五反田的一家店
You went to another place?
又去了另一家嗎？
We can't end the night with just dinner.
只是一頓飯怎麼夠呢？
We were there for about two hours and then I went home by train.
我們在那裡待了兩個小時 然後，我就坐電車回家了
Is it possible that it was stolen in the train?
會不會是在電車上被偷的？
I don't think so.
我想應該不會
I was holding the paper bag in front of me.
我一直把紙袋抱在胸前
You got drunk with that little amount? Either way, I can't count on your memory.
你喝那麼一點酒就醉了 也不知道你的記憶準不準
Why do you talk like…
你怎麼這麼說…
After I got home, I ended up going to sleep without working.
結果，我回到家裡，沒工作就睡著了
I noticed that the credit file was missing after I came to the office today.
今天回來辦公室之後 才發現信用檔案不見了
Then it is highly possible that it was stolen in either of the two restaurants.
那很有可能是在這兩家店的 其中一家被偷了，對吧？
I think so.
應該是吧
Oh, my God.
真是的
What if I have to take responsibility as the Section Chief
萬一因為你犯下的錯 連累身為融資課課長的我一起受罰
of the Finance Department?
你怎麼對得起我？
With all due respect…
恕我直言
What?
幹嘛？
Section Chief Kadota.
門田課長
As the Chief of the Finance Department, isn't it careless of you to be entertained
身為融資課課長的你 接受了一家要拒絕融資的企業的招待
by a company you won't be financing?
難道不是太輕率了嗎？
It has nothing to do with this problem.
這兩件事沒有關係吧？
Anyway, the entire responsibility lies with you for
總之 這次事件的所有責任都在你身上
taking out the credit file and getting it stolen.
都怪你把信用檔案帶出去 它才會被偷的
Keep that in mind.
你給我好好記住這點
Go to Sawada Kengyou by yourself.
你自己去澤田建業吧
It's not my business!
這可不關我的事
What was that? He talked as if this is all Mr. Matsuki's responsibility.
他是怎麼回事？ 說得好像全部責任都在松木先生身上
How frustrating.
真令人火大
Calm down.
好啦，冷靜點
But it's true that this is my fault.
不過，確實都是我的錯
But if Mr. Kadota hadn't asked you to join the dinner with his customer,
但如果門田課長 沒叫你跟他的客戶一起聚餐
you would have gone home and worked.
你就直接回家繼續工作了
Isn't Mr. Kadota partly responsible for this too?
難道門田課長 不應該承擔一部分責任嗎？
Hanasaki.
花咲
First, let's go to Sawada Kengyou and explain the situation.
我們先去澤田建業 跟他們解釋這件事吧
Here.
拿著
Yes.
是
Sawada Kengyou is a very solid company,
澤田建業是一家很可靠的公司
which makes me want to support them with all my heart.
我真心誠意想幫助他們
The President is very nice too.
澤田社長也是個很好的人
So I am hoping their additional loan gets approved.
所以，我一直希望 能幫他們申請到追加融資
Is it difficult?
遇到什麼困難了嗎？
Yes.
是的
They have been in the red, so it's tough.
他們最近的財務一直赤字 所以很難辦
Oh, no…
怎麼會這樣？
Our financial information leaked outside?
我們公司的財務資訊被洩露出去了？
I am sorry.
真的很抱歉
Of course, we are working hard to get it back.
當然，我們正在努力取回完整的資訊
Is everything really okay?
真的沒問題嗎？
If people in our industry see it, we will be over.
如果被同業發現，我們公司就完蛋了
Over…
完蛋？
We're pretending to be doing well,
我們表面上經營似乎很順利
but we've been in the red.
實際上財務一直處於赤字
We've managed to survive with a loan from Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
之前是靠東京第一銀行的貸款 才勉強熬過去的
If people find out our financial information,
如果被人知道我們的財務資訊
we will lose our customers.
客戶就不會再光顧我們了
We won't be able to keep going.
這樣一來，我們就無法做下去了
I am very sorry.
真的很抱歉
Will you bring it back for me?
你會幫我找回來吧？
You can do it, right Mr. Matsuki?
你能做到吧，松木先生？
This puts Mr. Matsuki in a pinch,
這下子松木先生陷入了困境
but it also puts Sawada Kengyou in a pinch too.
澤田建業也處於水深火熱呢
We have to solve this somehow for President Sawada.
為了澤田社長 無論如何都得好好解決啊
Let's go to see President Kasai
我們去見見昨天
of Shinagawa Butsuryu who entertained them last night.
招待他們的 品川物流公司的葛西社長吧
Yes.
好
SHINAGAWA BUTSURYU
（品川物流公司）
A document file?
文件檔案？
It was a very important file of a company.
是的，是某家公司的重要檔案
It was in a paper bag.
就裝在紙袋裡
I don't remember.
我不記得了
I wasn't paying much attention.
我也沒有特別留意
I understand.
這樣啊
President Kasai, you invited Kadota for dinner last night?
昨晚是社長你邀請門田課長的吧？
Yes. We are applying for a loan right now.
是的，我們最近正在申請融資
So I was hoping I could push things forward by doing that.
希望能用這種方式讓事情水到渠成
Do you hold dinner meetings often?
你經常做這樣的招待嗎？
Yes. We can talk well over a nice dinner and drinks.
是的，享用著美酒佳餚時 也比較好說話吧？
Mr. Matsuki, I'm sorry for dragging you to two places
我不知道你身上帶著那麼重要的資料
without knowing that you had such an important file.
還一連帶你去了兩家店，真的很抱歉
No. I wasn't careful.
不，是我自己不小心
I can call the places we went to last night.
我可以幫忙聯絡昨晚去過的那兩家店
It's okay. We will go there now.
沒關係，我們現在就過去
I see. I hope you can find it.
這樣啊，希望你們能找到
Yes. Thank you.
是啊，謝謝你
This is the room you used last night.
這是你們昨晚使用的房間
-Thank you. -I see, it was a private room.
-謝謝妳 -原來是包廂啊
Yes. I put my bag in here.
是的，我的公文包就放在這裡
It might not have been stolen in this room.
應該不是在這房間被偷的吧？
Okay. Let's go to the next one.
好吧，那我們去下一家吧
Was it in Gotanda?
是在五反田的吧？
Yes.
是的
But that place is…
不過，那家店是…
A hostess bar?
-夜總會？
-See you. Come again. -Yes.
-下次再來哦 -對
That's why I didn't want to bring Ms. Hanasaki.
所以我才不想帶花咲小姐來嘛
Mr. Matsuki, you come to this kind of bar too?
原來松木先生也會來這種店啊
No. Personally, I don't like these types of places…
不是，我自己才不喜歡這種地方…
I know, I know. Let's go.
好啦…走吧
Okay.
-好
Excuse me.
不好意思
How old are you?
妳幾歲了？
I am 27.
27歲
You're pretty old. You are too old to work here.
有點老了，不太適合在這裡工作呢
You're not here for the trial?
妳不是來體驗工作的嗎？
Trial?
體驗？
FREE TRIAL - NO EXPERIENCE NEEDED!
（入店體驗工作，無經驗可）
AGE 18 TO 23
（18歲至23歲）
He assumed I came for the trial and tells me I'm pretty old. How rude!
他誤會我是來體驗工作的 還說我老，真沒禮貌
I will take your bag.
請把包包存放在這裡
Here.
好的
So you have to leave your bag at the entrance, huh.
所以進來的時候 必須由店家保管包包呢
-Yes. -Mr. Soma.
-是的 -相馬
If it was stolen, it most likely happened here.
要是被偷的話，這家店嫌疑最大
And the caller was a woman too.
而且打來的那個人也是女性的聲音
Then the culprit is in this bar?
也就是說，犯人就在這家店裡？
Excuse me.
不好意思
Is there a particular girl you'd like?
你們想要指名哪位小姐？
Oh… ah… yes. Matsuki!
是，松木
Yes.
是
EMILY
（繪美里）
Emily, Honoka, and Sara, please.
那就繪美里小姐 穗花小姐和沙羅小姐吧
Sure.
好的
Excuse me.
-打攪了
I'm Emily.
我是繪美里
I'm Honoka.
我是穗花
Hello.
妳們好
You look so happy.
一臉色瞇瞇的樣子
Move aside.
坐一邊啦
Mr. Matsuki!
松木先生
-You came again! -Hi.
-你今天也來啦 -妳好
Stop looking so serious. They will be suspicious.
別一副嚴肅的臉，她們會起疑心的
Mr. Matsuki, you work for a bank, right?
松木先生是在銀行上班吧？
Yes.
是啊
Then are you the Branch Manager?
那這位是分行經理囉？
Something like that.
算是吧？
He is telling a lie.
開始撒謊了
He said that he met many pretty girls last night,
他說昨晚在這裡看到很多漂亮妹妹
so I came along.
我就跟來了
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的嗎？ -是啊
Thank you for waiting. Here is Sara.
久等了，這位是沙羅小姐
Hello. I am Sara.
歡迎光臨，我是沙羅
I'm glad to see you again.
很高興再見到你呢
Hi.
妳好
Branch Manager makes lots of money, right?
分行經理應該賺不少錢吧？
No. I just get used to seeing a lot of money.
哪有？我是看錢看習慣了
I envy you. We don't have any at all.
好羡慕啊，我們都很缺錢呢
Really? I thought you were paid well.
是嗎？我還以為這裡的薪資不錯呢
Tomorrow is payday.
對了，明天發工資
You are right.
對哦
-I can't wait. -I see.
-都等不及了呢 -是嗎？
Excuse me.
不好意思，失陪一下
Your lipstick is the latest color.
妳的口紅是今年流行的顏色吧？
Yes.
是啊
This is a nice clutch. Is it the latest design?
這個手拿包也很華麗呢 是這季的新款嗎？
Yes.
是的
Did Mr. Matsuki leave anything when he came last night?
松木先生昨晚來的時候 是不是忘了什麼東西在這裡？
It's an important document.
好像是很重要的文件呢
I don't know anything.
我什麼都不知道
There's going to be trouble if we can't find it.
找不到的話就糟糕了
We may have to report it to the police.
可能需要報警呢
Police? Does that mean the police will be asking us questions?
報警？所以警察會過來審問我們嗎？
No. We will report it as a missing item.
不是啦，我是指報失
Sure, of course.
是這樣啊
RESTAURANT HANASAKI
（花咲居酒屋）
Sara is suspicious.
沙羅小姐有點可疑
Suspicious of what?
什麼可疑？
I only said we "may" report to the police,
我只說我們可能會報警
but she became very flustered.
她就變得慌慌張張的
Is Sara the culprit then?
所以犯人是沙羅小姐嗎？
We don't know yet.
還不確定
But she could have left her seat for a while to steal the file.
但她有可能在接待客人的中途 離席偷出文件
Do you think she did it for the money?
是為了錢嗎？
They were saying that their work is tough.
她們都說做那行很辛苦呢
Shall we check if she is in debt?
要不要調查看看她有沒有欠債？
We might find a lead.
可能會找到什麼線索
That's a good point.
好主意
I don't think you can do it.
應該查不到吧？
Why?
為什麼？
Sara at Paradise. That's all we know.
我們只知道她是天堂夜總會的沙羅
I see. That's a nickname and we don't know her real name.
對哦，這是化名 我們不知道她的真名呢
Can we ask the bar?
不能去店裡問嗎？
Do you think they'll give us her personal information
我們又不是警察 你覺得那麼私人的資訊
when we're not the police?
他們會告訴我們嗎？
We are very close, though.
都快真相大白了，真是的
If we want to investigate Sara any further we'll have to report it to the police.
如果想要進一步調查沙羅小姐的話 就只能報警了
But we're not certain enough to do that yet.
但我們現在只是懷疑，沒辦法這麼做
You are right.
就是說啊
Let's report to the Branch Manager tomorrow and think about the plan.
我們明天向竹內經理報告 再考慮接下來的對策吧
Okay.
-好的
I'll go home.
那我先回去了
Are you going home, Mr. Soma?
相馬，你要走了嗎？
Yes. Thanks.
是的，謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝
-See you tomorrow. -Take care.
-辛苦你了 -路上小心
Oh, I forgot I ran out of sudachi. I'll go buy them.
對了，我忘了酢橘用完了 我現在去買
Do you have to get them now?
一定要現在買嗎？
I'm going to be tactful and step out. Good luck.
如此機智的我，當然要現在出門了 加油
Enjoy.
請慢慢享用
-Yes. -Hey.
-是 -夠了
Well…
真是的
I got an X-mark.
這可是個大汙點呢
X-mark?
汙點？
I will have to take responsibility for what I've done.
我肯定得為自己的過錯承擔責任
Once you get an X-mark, that's the end.
一旦有汙點就完了
That's banks for you.
銀行就是這樣的地方
That's not true. That's definitely not true.
沒這種事，才不是這樣的呢
Everyone can make a mistake.
每個人都會犯錯
But that shouldn't end everything. That's wrong.
不應該犯一次錯就完蛋 這樣太奇怪了
Everyone has as many chances as they need to try again.
不管是誰，都應該擁有 無數次重來的機會
You shouldn't be saying things like that, Mr. Matsuki.
你不能說那樣的話，松木先生
Ms. Hanasaki.
花咲小姐
Besides, what you should be thinking about the most right now
而且，你現在最應該擔心的
is Sawada Kengyou, isn't it?
應該是澤田建業吧？
You can feel blue after we settle this problem.
等事情解決之後，再來頹廢也不遲
You are right.
沒錯
I will think about what I can do for now.
我應該想想自己現在能做什麼
Yes.
是的
Eat some more.
快吃…
I didn't eat at all.
我都還沒吃呢
You need to eat to gain energy.
要吃東西才有體力啊
Yes.
是
Is that the girl you like?
是你喜歡的女孩子嗎？
Ms. Saito.
齋藤大姐
-You like young girls, huh. -No…
-喜歡這麼年輕的妹妹啊？ -不是的
Guys! I got something.
你們看我發現了什麼
Ms. Saito!
齋藤大姐
I was just joking.
開玩笑的啦
-Oh. She's our customer. -What?
-這不是我們的顧客嗎？ -什麼？
I see her often at the ATM.
我常看到她在提款機那裡哦
Are you sure?
妳確定嗎？
I've been working here for ten years.
我在這裡工作十年了
I remember the customers.
不會認錯顧客的臉的
Thank you very much!
真的太謝謝妳了
She's a customer of Gotanda Branch?
她是五反田分行的顧客？
Yes. I heard that she uses our ATM very often.
對，聽說她經常使用這裡的提款機
If she uses the ATM, we can check her account number.
使用提款機的話，就能查到她的帳號
-Then we will know who Sara is. -Yes.
-那我們就能知道沙羅小姐的身分了 -沒錯
But we don't know when she is coming.
但是，我們不知道她什麼時候會來啊
That's right. We have no time to just wait for her.
是啊，我們可沒時間等了
She may come today.
她今天可能會來
How do you know?
你怎麼知道？
Tomorrow is payday.
明天發工資
You are right.
對哦
I can't wait.
都等不及了呢
Today is payday at Paradise.
今天是天堂夜總會發薪的日子
She will come for a withdrawal.
她肯定會來領錢
She isn't coming.
沒來啊
Maybe she's using a different ATM today.
可能是用其他地方的提款機了
Sorry.
真對不起
Don't give up. Let's wait.
別放棄，再等等吧
Yes.
是
Look. We met her in Paradise.
看，這是天堂夜總會的小姐
Emily.
繪美里
You remember her name?
你還記得人家的名字啊？好厲害
But we need Sara.
但我們等的沙羅小姐…
She is not here yet.
沒有來啊
Thank you very much.
謝謝
I wonder if she's not coming today.
果然她今天不會來了吧？
Here she comes.
來了
-Which one? -Where?
-哪位？ -在哪裡？
Here. It's her.
這個啊
Is that really her?
-什麼？ -這真的是她嗎？
True, she looks different today with jeans,
她素顏穿便服的樣子
and no makeup.
跟在店裡不一樣
But that's Sara.
但這個人就是沙羅小姐
Ms. Saito. Please.
齊藤大姐，拜託了
Okay.
好的
ATM ROOM
（提款機室）
I'm ready.
準備好了
Okay.
知道了
Which machine is she going to use?
她會用幾號機呢？
We won't know until the last moment.
不到最後一刻不知道啊
-Number three! -Mr. Matsuki. Number three.
-三號 -松木先生，是三號機
-Number three. -Okay.
-好的
IN USE
（使用中）
OPEN
（開啓）
BUSY
（取得資訊中）
ELECTRONIC JOURNAL
（電子帳簿）
This is who she is.
這就是她的真實身分
Yuriko Kawashima.
川島百合子
That's Sara's real name.
這就是沙羅小姐的本名
Yes. She opened a bank account at this branch two years ago.
是的，她兩年前在這間分行開戶
Paradise pays her about 500,000 yen every month.
每個月在天堂夜總會獲得的工資 大約是50萬
Her credit card payment is between 250,000 to 300,000 yen.
信用卡的結算額是25萬至30萬
Rent is 200,000 yen.
房租20萬
That's a pretty extravagant lifestyle.
相當奢侈的生活啊
If she pays the water and energy bills, she will be in the red.
再支付水費和煤電費 她就入不敷出了
Her income is 500,000 yen, but she spends 600,000 yen.
收入50萬，花費卻是60萬左右
There is a transfer.
這裡還有轉帳呢
She's receiving it every month.
而且是每個月固定會收到
-Who's transferring it? -Norio Kasai?
-轉帳給她的人是… -葛西紀夫
Norio Kasai!
葛西紀夫
It's President Kasai.
是葛西社長
President Kasai…
葛西社長？
SHINAGAWA BUTSURYU
（品川物流公司）
President Kasai is regularly transferring money into Sara's account?
葛西社長定期轉帳給 沙羅小姐的帳戶？
Is she his mistress?
是情人嗎？
-What? -What do you mean?
-什麼？ -什麼意思？
I am not quite sure,
我也不是很確定
but Sara might be President Kasai's mistress.
不過 沙羅小姐可能是葛西社長的情人
Then they're accomplices?
所以，他們是同夥嗎？
President Kasai asked Sara to steal the credit file?
是葛西社長 要沙羅小姐偷信用檔案的嗎？
Shinagawa Butsuryu isn't doing well financially, right?
品川物流的經營狀態不太好吧？
It is very bad. We are planning to turn down their loan application too.
相當糟糕 我們正打算拒絕他們的融資申請
He's unbelievable!
真是難以置信
Matsuki! What are you doing? Go to Kasai and bring it back.
松木，你還坐在這裡幹嘛？ 去葛西那裡把資料拿回來啊
Wait a minute.
等等
Even if we approach President Kasai,
就算我們去找葛西社長
if he feigns innocence, we'll have no solution.
他也可以假裝不知道 那我們一樣是束手無策
That's right.
確實
Then what should we do?
那該怎麼辦呢？
Yes.
是
Wait a moment.
等一下
The woman is calling.
是那個女人打來的
What are you going to do?
你打算怎麼辦？
Let's pay the reward money.
付酬金吧
Branch Manager. If you do such a thing…
竹內經理，如果這麼做的話…
Our priority right now is to take back that credit file.
我們現在的首要任務 是取回那個信用檔案
I'll talk to her.
幫我接通
I'm Takeuchi, the Branch Manager.
我是分行經理竹內
Yes. I would like to pay you a reward.
是，我可以給妳酬金
Thank you very much.
真是麻煩妳了
3 p.m. tomorrow at the lobby of the Tokyo Hills Hotel.
明天3點，東京希爾斯飯店大廳嗎？
I understand.
我知道了
Are you sure it's okay for us to do this?
真的要這麼做嗎？
It's only natural that they reward us since we're returning what we found.
把東西物歸原主 接受酬金是理所應當的吧
Don't worry.
別擔心
But I didn't find it.
但那東西不是我撿回來的
You just follow what I say.
按我說的做就對了
Now our branch has a big X-mark.
現在我們分行留下那麼大的汙點
-It's your fault! Do you understand? -Branch Manager.
-都是你的錯，知道嗎？ -竹內經理
Please take me with you tomorrow.
明天…請讓我跟你一起去吧
I will take all the responsibility.
這件事…我會負全責的…
No. Don't get involved with this any further.
不用了，你別再牽涉其中了
No matter how this problem is solved, you'll face disciplinary action.
這個問題無論怎麼解決 你都需要接受處分
Be prepared.
做好心理準備吧
Yes.
是
I reported to the top management with the Branch Manager.
我和竹內經理一起向上頭報告了
What did they say?
他們怎麼說？
Of course, they got mad
當然是很生氣啊
for agreeing to pay the million yen without getting their permission.
說為什麼擅自決定給她100萬
Understandable.
也是啊
I was scolded by the Director saying that I should have reported to him first.
部長還罵我說應該先向他報告呢
Now that this problem has become this big,
現在事態嚴重
the branch will have to take serious responsibility for it.
分行要負起的責任可大了
Will Mr. Matsuki get punished?
松木先生會被處分嗎？
Probably. His earnest attitude towards his job backfired on him.
應該吧？ 那傢伙的工作熱情讓他倒大楣了
I think banks need someone earnest and serious like Mr. Matsuki.
可是，銀行就是需要像松木先生那樣 熱情認真的職員啊
I think so too.
我也這麼想
I am going to Sawada Kengyou.
我去一趟澤田建業
The bank can't help running around in a panic about what happened.
銀行為了這次的事不知所措 也是沒辦法的
But Mr. Sawada is probably more worried.
但澤田社長會更擔憂吧？
So I will go and inform him.
我想早點去通知他
-Okay. Go see him. -Yes.
-好的，妳去吧 -是
-Please come in. -Thank you.
-請進 -打擾了
Mr. Matsuki?
松木先生？
Ms. Hanasaki!
花咲小姐
Why are you here?
你在這裡幹嘛？
I wanted to do what I can do right now.
我想盡可能做點能力所及的事
You're writing the proposal for an additional loan?
這是追加融資的提案書嗎？
Since I lost the credit file, I came here to see the documents.
我把信用檔案弄不見了 所以就來這裡找資料
He said that he wanted to do this by any means.
他說無論如何都想完成這個
I see.
原來如此
Mr. Matsuki is doing his best. I understand that.
你已經盡力了，我知道的
I'll make some tea.
我幫妳泡個茶吧
Mr. Matsuki, you're a great banker.
松木先生 你真的是很好的融資職員呢
No. I just want Sawada Kengyou's loan application to move forward
不，就算我要離開了 我也希望能成功申請到
even after I leave.
澤田建業的融資
I'll ask the Branch Manager too.
我會去求竹內經理的
In order to do that, I have to prepare a good proposal document.
要成功的話 就必須準備一份完美的提案書
I am very sorry. Please wait.
非常抱歉，拜託了
I promise to pay you by the end of the month.
我跟你保證，月底一定會支付的
Yes. Thank you.
是，謝謝你了
Excuse me.
不好意思
I have to keep the company for my employees.
為了我的員工 我一定要想辦法保住我的公司啊
Mr. Soma, I really can't forgive Mr. Kasai.
相馬，我真的無法原諒葛西社長
Is there anything we can do?
我們什麼都做不了嗎？
I talked to the Legal Department.
我跟法務部商量過了
What he has done is regarded as extortion.
他的行為已經構成敲詐罪
Then we will go to the hotel tomorrow…
那我們明天去飯店…
President Kasai won't appear.
葛西社長不會出現的
He used Sara for everything from stealing the file, to making the calls.
偷文件和打電話的人都是沙羅小姐
Sara will most likely come to receive the reward money.
明天來拿酬金的 應該也是沙羅小姐吧？
I guess so.
說得也是
If anything happens, he will probably blame everything on her.
萬一出事了 他就可以把所有罪都推給沙羅小姐
In order to prove that President Kasai is behind all this,
如果要證明葛西社長是幕後黑手
we will need Sara to testify against him.
唯有讓沙羅小姐指證他才行
Mr. Soma. Let's ask her to testify.
相馬，我們去拿證詞吧
Huh?
什麼？
SAWADA KENGYOU
（澤田建業）
-Are you the Branch Manager? -Yes.
-是分行經理嗎？ -是的
Thank you very much for bringing us the important document.
謝謝妳把那麼重要的文件還給我們
Please take this.
請收下這個
Here you go.
那這個還你
Yes, this is it.
確實是我要的文件
If you take that money,
如果妳收下這筆錢
we will have to take you to court.
我們就必須起訴妳了
Is that okay with you, Sara?
這樣也無所謂嗎，沙羅小姐？
I mean, Ms. Yuriko Kawashima.
不對，是川島百合子小姐
SARA (YURIKO)
（沙羅，百合子）
What are you doing? Did you receive the money?
妳在幹嘛呢？錢收到了嗎？
By money, do you mean the money you were trying to extort?
你說的錢 是指你敲詐我們的那筆錢嗎？
Will you tell us everything, Mr. Kasai?
請你坦白吧，葛西先生
What's everything?
坦白什麼呢？
Sara was honest and told us everything.
沙羅小姐全都告訴我們了
She said she stole the credit file.
她說是她偷走信用檔案的
I stole the file.
偷走檔案的人是我
Since Sara is your lover,
沙羅小姐是你的情人
she has no choice but to follow your instructions.
她沒辦法不聽從你的指示
Will you admit everything?
你就承認吧
Damn.
可惡
What's wrong with that?
是我指示的又怎麼樣？
First of all, this is all the bank's fault.
反正一開始就是銀行的錯
I wanted to rebuild my company,
我為了重建公司
so I took Mr. Kadota out for meals and drinks many times.
招待門田課長好多次了
But you never planned to finance us from the beginning, right?
但你從一開始就沒打算給我融資 對吧？
That's not true. I assess the loan in a fair manner--
不是這樣的 我可是很公正地審批你的融資…
That's a lie.
別說謊了！
I asked you out for a dinner on that day
我那天為了取得融資
to get approval for the loan.
而招待你
But what you said changed everything.
可是，你一句話就讓一切都改變了
Mr. Kadota, please help us with the loans.
門田課長，融資的事…請幫幫忙吧
You should know by now…
你還不清楚嗎？
With your business performance,
憑你公司那樣的業績
we can't give you an additional loan.
是不可能申請到追加融資的
But…
可是…
A bank is not a charity.
銀行可不是慈善機構啊
Mr. Kadota, you better not…
門田課長，你說得…
I said no.
就是不行
That's too bad.
太糟了呢
So I changed my mind.
於是，我改變了主意
If I stole Mr. Matsuki's file,
如果偷走了松木先生的文件
Tokyo Daiichi Bank would be in trouble,
東京第一銀行惹上了大麻煩
and you would be punished too, Mr. Kadota.
那門田課長你也會被處罰吧？
I also thought I could get a reward
而且，如果我說東西是撿到的
if I said that I found it.
還有酬金呢
Steal a file from that paper bag that says Sawada Kengyou on it.
去把那個紙袋裡 寫著澤田建業的檔案偷出來
This is all because of the bank. It's Mr. Kadota's fault.
這都是銀行的錯，是門田課長的錯
What are you talking about? Branch Manager!
你胡說什麼呢？竹內經理
He is trying to pin the blame on me.
他這是想把責任推到我身上
You are right.
確實
Kadota went out with you
門田他
although he was planning to refuse the loan.
已經決定拒絕你的融資請求 又接受你的招待
What he did is wrong.
這樣做是不可原諒的
We will investigate him thoroughly in this regard.
我們會仔細調查清楚這件事
However, Mr. Kasai…
可是，葛西先生
that will not get erase what you have done.
這並不會抹滅你所犯下的錯
In the end, I didn't get any money.
說到底，我又沒拿到錢
I returned the file, so the bank didn't lose anything.
檔案也歸還給你們了 銀行沒有任何損失
Isn't that enough?
沒什麼大不了的啊
I told you, it's all his fault. I didn't do anything wrong.
我都說了，全都是這傢伙的錯 我沒做錯什麼
With all due respect…
恕我直言
do you know how much President Sawada suffered the last two days?
你知不知道這兩天 澤田社長有多麼苦惱？
As a fellow business manager, don't you understand that?
同樣是社長 你難道不理解他的心情嗎？
What'll happen to the company?
公司要怎麼辦？
How will he support the employees, if the company goes bankrupt?
如果破產的話 員工們的生計又要怎麼辦？
President Sawada was worrying about all that.
澤田社長一直在擔心著這些
Your selfish behavior kept an innocent person
你那自私的行為讓無辜的人
awake all night with worry.
一整晚擔心受怕、無法入眠
How do you not know that?
你連這點都不明白嗎？
What you did is wrong.
身為一名經營者，你絕對是犯了錯
What? Just shut up.
什麼啊？閉嘴
No, I won't!
我不要！
There's more to this.
還不止這樣
There is one more person
還有一個人
who is suffering a lot.
他也同樣飽受痛苦
It's Mr. Matsuki.
那就是松木先生
Mr. Matsuki has been working hard in the Finance Department because
松木先生一直投身於融資課
he wants to help out small companies.
就是為了協助中小型企業
He is making an effort to support Sawada Kengyou
他想盡一切辦法去幫助
because they are having financial difficulties.
面對財務困境的澤田建業
Sadly, he broke the rules of the bank by doing that.
他甚至違反了銀行的規則 把資料拿回家加班
Because you stole the credit file,
就是因為你偷走了信用檔案
Mr. Matsuki will have to take responsibility.
松木先生需要為此負上責任
He may lose his job at the Finance Department.
還有可能失去融資課的工作
Can you still say that you haven't done anything bad?
你還有臉說自己什麼都沒做錯嗎？
Someone who works hard shouldn't be penalized for it.
怎麼可以把認真努力工作的人 當傻子呢？
Those who are earnestly working hard are not evaluated.
踏實工作的人沒有回報
And those who cheat get the benefit.
狡猾的騙子卻得到好處
That's definitely wrong!
這是大錯特錯！
Mr. Matsuki.
松木先生
Everything was settled.
一切都解決了哦
Thank you.
謝謝你們
-I'm relieved. -Mr. Matsuki.
-太好了 -松木先生
President Sawada!
澤田社長
Thank you. Thank you very much.
謝謝你，真是太謝謝你了
I am sorry for causing you trouble.
給您添麻煩了
Don't worry.
沒關係
The file was returned safe and sound.
文件都還回來了
Please continue working with us.
今後還得繼續拜託你呢
Yes. I am more than happy to work with you.
是，今後請您多多關照
The additional loan to Sawada Kengyou was approved.
澤田建業的追加融資好像順利通過了
Really?
真的嗎？
That's good. Mr. Matsuki was working so hard to prepare the proposal.
太好了 松木先生很努力地準備提案書呢
Right.
是啊
But he will be transferred, right?
可是他會被調職，對吧？
Yes. To Okayama Branch.
是啊，被調去岡山分行
I know someone has to take responsibility,
我知道必須有人為這件事負責
but isn't it wrong that Mr. Matsuki is the only one that's being punished?
但怎麼可以只處分松木先生一個呢？
But there are people who see everything.
老天爺可是有眼的
Mr. Kadota's numerous wrongdoings came to light during the investigation,
門田課長其他的不正當行為被發現
so he received a strict disciplinary action of one month's suspension.
受到停職一個月的重罰
We didn't report President Kasai to the police,
葛西社長沒有受警方調查
but our bank cancelled all business with his company.
但我們銀行 已經終止跟他公司的所有合作
He may not be able to maintain his company anymore.
這樣下去 他的公司應該也撐不了多久
In short, the bank is not completely rotten yet.
總之，銀行也還沒完全腐敗呢
Yes.
是的
I am so sorry.
非常抱歉
Senior Executive Director Doujima took the first move
堂島專務更迅速地採取了行動
to handle the police and the media.
去應付警方以及媒體
I see.
是嗎？
He was one step ahead of us regarding this case.
他可是比我們搶先了一步呢
One step ahead of us?
比我們搶先了一步？
Yes.
是的
That's fine.
那很好啊
Tokyo Daiichi Bank was able to maintain their pride.
只要東京第一銀行的聲譽沒有影響
It doesn't matter who took care of it.
誰去處理都可以吧？
Am I right?
對嗎？
Yes.
您說的沒錯
Excuse me.
我先出去了
Doujima!
堂島
-By the way, Hanasaki. -Yes?
-對了，花咲 -是
Matsuki said that he is leaving for Okayama on the 10:50 a.m. bullet train.
松木說他會坐 今天10點50分的新幹線去岡山哦
Today?
今天嗎？
-This is a gift for him. Pass it to him. -Yes.
-這是餞別禮物，幫我交給他 -好的
Let's go together, Mr. Soma.
你也一起去吧
I… I have a meeting with the Director. Sorry.
我…啊，部長有事要找我談 拜託妳了
Yes.
喔，好的
BRANCH INSPECTION
（分行稽核班）
Mr. Matsuki.
松木先生
Ms. Hanasaki.
花咲小姐
This is from Mr. Soma.
這個是相馬給你的
Thank you very much.
謝謝妳
I'll miss you when you go to Okayama.
你要去岡山了，好捨不得啊
I'm so thankful to you and Mr. Soma for working hard to
妳和相馬先生為了我 想盡辦法查明真相
find out the truth for me.
我真的很謝謝你們
I couldn't help you much.
我也沒幫上什麼忙
I am fine.
我沒事哦
I'm surprised at how I'm not feeling down at all.
我也很意外自己一點都不覺得失落
I once said that it's the end when you get a X-mark,
我之前還說，在銀行這個地方
and that's how banks work.
一旦有汙點就完蛋了
But I was wrong.
但我錯了
Wherever I go, there are things I can do.
無論去到哪裡 必然有自己能力所及的事
There will always be a way, as long as I don't give up.
只要不放棄，就一定有出路
I learned that from you, Ms. Hanasaki.
這是我從妳身上學到的，花咲小姐
Mr. Matsuki…
松木先生…
The bank will change if there are more people like you.
要是有更多像花咲妳這樣的人 銀行一定會改變的
I want to be like you. I honestly do.
我也想像妳一樣，我是這樣想的
I will come back with confidence.
我一定會抬頭挺胸地回來
When I do, will you go out with me to have a nice meal? This time…
到時候 妳願意跟我一起去吃好吃的嗎？
This time with just the two of us.
就只有我們兩個人一起
Yes.
好啊
See you.
那…
-I'll do my best. -Yes.
-我先走了 -好
This time with just the two of us…
“就只有我們兩個人一起”
Could it be…
難道說…
No way.
不會吧？
Mr. Matsuki moved away, huh?
松木被調走了啊？
The biggest fish is the one that always gets away.
怎麼溜掉了最大的那條魚呢？
-That's big! -That's enough, Dad.
-好大 -別說這些了，爸
I see. In the end, he left without confessing his true feelings.
這樣啊 結果，那傢伙沒有告白就離開了
What?
什麼？
Was there something going on?
小舞，他有說那樣的話嗎？
Not at all…
沒有啦…
Wait. What he said when he left…
等等，他離開前說的那個…
Could it be…
難道說…
When he asked me out for dinner and the grilled meat…
所以，他之前約我吃飯烤肉…
That's right.
就是這麼回事啊
Why didn't you tell me? You even came with us to eat grilled meat!
那你怎麼不跟我說？ 你還跟我們一起去烤肉呢
Because you asked me to come.
那是妳叫我一起去的啊
What should I do? What?
那怎麼辦？
Mai, it's still not too late. Go to Okayama.
小舞，現在還不遲，去岡山吧
-No way. -Just go.
-不行啦 -去吧！
You can do it if you have the will.
只要有心就能成事
Okayama?
去岡山？
Attacked?
-被襲擊了？
Branch Manager was pushed down the stairs.
分行經理被人推下樓梯了
Stop insulting me, Branch Inspectors.
區區一個稽核員，竟敢那麼無禮
They had a fight concerning bankruptcy.
因為公司破產的事，曾經有過糾紛呢
That was harassment.
那是霸凌
-Do it over. -What a stupid man.
-重寫！ -愚蠢的男人
The position you gained by doing that,
靠這些手段得來的地位
is not worth anything!
一點價值也沒有！